The future belongs to those who fight.
Worldbreaker is a science fiction, action, horror
film directed by Brad Anderson.
Five years ago, a tear in the fabric of reality brought creatures to our
world from an alternate dimension bent on our destruction.
A father hides his daughter on an island to keep her safe while he
prepares her for survival and the battles to come.
But when the world is about to break, no place is safe.
Mom, played by Milla Jovovich.
Dad, played by Luke Evans.
Willa, played by Billie Boullet.
Soldier #1, played by Meadow Williams.
Rosie, played by Mila Harris.
The Man, played by Kevin Glynn.
World Breaker is a 2025 science fiction action horror film
directed by Brad Anderson and written by Joshua Rollins.
It stars Luke Evans and Milla Jovovich.
The film explores themes of monster, climate change, global warming.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.